doitbest.com 2017-02-10

# Privacy Policy - Do it Best

By using or accessing our website you signify your acknowledgment and assent to the Privacy Policy set forth below.  If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this website. Do it Best can revise this policy at any time by updating this posting, and your use after such change signifies your acceptance of the changed terms.  Please check this policy periodically for changes.

Do it Best understands that our customers are concerned about privacy online. This policy is intended to help you understand how Do it Best Commerce Company, LLC and its affiliates ("Do it Best," "we," or "us") collect, use and safeguard the information you provide on our website.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to the use or disclosure of information that is collected or obtained by us through means other than this website.

### **PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION**

If you browse our website, you may generally do so anonymously without providing any personal information.  However, there are cases where we collect personal data – you will know this data is being collected because you will have to provide it such as by filling out a form.  We collect personally identifiable and transactional information when you: (1) purchase products or services from the site (2) register for an account, (3) request to receive additional information regarding products and services, or (4) send us a question. If you choose not to give information we request, you can still visit most of our website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services.  We may combine the information you submit under your account with other information that we may receive from you, from third parties, or with other public demographic information.

In case you change your mind or wish to update or delete your personal information, we will endeavor to correct, update or remove the personal data you give us.  You can do this by contacting Customer Care using the contact information specified below.

###  **PRODUCT ORDERS**

When you place an order for a product, we need to know your contact information, shipping information, e-mail address and payment card information (such as payment card name, card number, CVV and expiration date).   This information is required so that payment can be authorized by a third party payment processor (the “Payment Processor”) that we have retained to process payments made via the site. All payment card information is provided directly to the Payment Processor and not to Do it Best (i.e., we do not receive or store your credit card information in connection with payments authorized through the site). All Internet transactions with the Payment Processor are performed on a server that uses industry standard encryption technology to protect your payment card information from being obtained by unauthorized third parties. Use of your payment and transaction information will be subject to the privacy policies of the Payment Processor and your credit card issuer. We are not responsible for any errors by the Payment Processor or for any security breaches suffered by such entity. In connection with your use of the site, Do it Best may obtain certain payment transaction details from the Payment Processor, which we will use solely in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  We also use your order information to fulfill your order and send an order or shipping confirmation, as well as notify you of your order status.

### **MARKETING MESSAGES**

When you purchase products online from us, request product information or otherwise provide us with personal information, we may automatically place you on a list to receive promotional mailings and e-mails regarding special offers from Do it Best, its affiliates and the Do it Best member with whom you have placed your order. If you do not wish to receive these messages, you can simply utilize the opt-out method detailed in the message, respond to any email by telling us that you do not want to receive any future communications, or contact Customer Care using the contact information specified below. You may not opt-out of receiving essential updates regarding your account.

### **USE AND SHARING OF PERSONAL DATA**

We use the personal information that is collected through the website to better serve users, customize their shopping experience, and improve the content of our website. We may use personal information about you and your use of the site to offer you tailored content and to notify you of offers (concerning Do it Best, its affiliates and the Do it Best member with whom you have placed your order). Personal information that you provide will be used for marketing and promotional purposes only by Do it Best and its corporate affiliates and the Do it Best member with whom you have placed your order. 

 We may share your personal information as follows:

  * Among our corporate affiliates; 

  * With the Do it Best member with whom you have placed your order;

  * With third party agents we have hired to help us provide a good or service you have requested (for example, in connection with your order, we would provide your payment card information to the Payment Processor and your address to a shipping company);

  * With third party companies that we have retained to assist us for processing, security, credit or fraud prevention purposes (and who have agreed in writing not to use the information for unauthorized purposes); and

  * In the Special Cases set forth below.

We do not rent or sell to third parties your personally identifiable information for such parties’ own marketing purposes.

 We may share statistical or aggregated non-personal information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. This data is used to customize our website content and advertising to deliver a better experience to our users.

### **ONLINE TRACKING AND PASSIVE COLLECTION**

Our web servers collect general data (“Usage Information”) pertaining to users of this site and the mobile devices and programs from which they access this site. Usage information can include IP address, domain name, referring web page, browser type, mobile device type, device operating system, device settings, and information about the way you use your device or this site (such as the length of time spent and the pages accessed while visiting this website). The Usage Information collected does not, in and of itself, identify you personally, but we may link it to personal information. Usage Information is collected to help us manage and administer our website, to improve the content of our website, to customize and improve the website user experience, to measure the effectiveness of our advertising, and for security and fraud detection purposes. Usage Information is gathered using the following methods: (1) cookies, (2) web beacons (a.k.a. clear gifs), (3) conversion tracking, (4) web analytics, (5) third party ad serving mechanisms, and (6) general detection and use of your internet protocol (IP) address or domain name. We do not collect personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities across third party web sites (and thus do not monitor your browser’s Do Not Track indicator).

### **Cookies**

### 

"Cookie" technology is used on this web site. The cookie is sent by our web site to your browser and then it may be stored on your computer or computer system.  Cookies may be used to recognize you as a user and tailor our web site to your interests based on your previous online shopping preferences within the site. For example, if you visit the plumbing section of our site, the site would "remember" the visit and let you know of specials, new products, or related plumbing projects upon a future web site visit. Cookies used by this site do not contain any personally identifiable information. If for any reason you don’t want to take advantage of cookies, you may have your browser not accept them, although this may disable or render unusable some of the features of our site.   You also have the ability to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. This enables you to choose to accept or reject the cookie. 

### W **eb Beacons**

Web pages on this site or messages you receive from us may contain a small graphic image called a web beacon (sometimes called a web bug or clear gif).  Web beacons are designed to allow us or a third party to collect Usage Information and monitor user activity on our site (such as when you view the web page, advertisement, or message that contains the web beacon). We may permit third parties hired by us to place web beacons on our sites or in messages sent on our behalf for purposes of collecting these same types of Usage Information for web analytics, processing, security or fraud detection purposes. 

### **Conversion Tracking**

Search engines offer a feature called “conversion tracking” which is a way to track clicks to sales from either search results or ads on search engines. Using either web beacons or visible images, depending upon the search engine, the search engine notes and saves information in a cookie with non-personal information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. Information is gathered in the aggregate, without unique personal data. Conversion tracking allows the search engine company and Do it Best to track clicks to sales, including the number of clicks (“visits”) it takes before a purchase is made and permits us to measure the effectiveness of our search engine  participation.] 

### **Web Analytics**

We may use third party web analytics tools (such as Google® Analytics) to collect Usage Information to help us understand how visitors engage with our site.  These third party services may use cookies, web beacons or other collection technologies to collect such Usage Information. 

### **Advertising**

We may use the services of a third party advertising company to serve ads on our site. Such ad serving may involve the use of web beacons or cookies to manage and target advertisements and for market research analysis.

### **SECURITY**

We use security measures consistent with industry practice to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While we use reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, we cannot guarantee that data will always remain secure due to transmission errors, outside events, third party hacking or other causes. We will comply with all privacy laws and make any legally required disclosures regarding breaches of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of personal data consistent with our ability to determine the scope of a breach and our obligations to law enforcement.

### **CONSENT TO TRANSFER**

This Website is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to Do it Best will be transferred to the United States. By using this Website or providing us with your information you consent to this transfer.

### **SPECIAL CASES**

Do it Best reserves the right to disclose user information in special cases, when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Do it Best website users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.  We may disclose personal information without notice to you in response to a subpoena or when we believe in good faith that the law permits it or to respond to an emergency situation. 

In the event Do it Best or its subsidiaries or affiliates or their assets are sold, merged or otherwise involved in a corporate transaction, your personal information will likely be transferred as part of that transaction.  We reserve to right to transfer your information without your consent in such a situation; provided that we will make reasonable efforts to see that your privacy preferences are honored by the transferee.

Specific areas or pages of this website may include additional or different provisions relating to collection and disclosure of personal information.  In the event of a conflict between such provisions and this Privacy Policy, such specific terms shall control.

**POLICIES FOR CHILDREN**

Do it Best does not knowingly collect or use any personal information from users under 13 years of age. No information should be submitted to this site by guests under 13 years of age, and guests under 13 years old are not allowed to register for our contests, newsletter, clubs or activities.

### LINKED SITES

Please be advised that our web site contains links to third-party websites.  The linked sites are not under our control, and we are not responsible for the contents or privacy practices of any linked site or any link on a linked site.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

Do it Best reserves the right to change or update this policy, or any other policy or practice, at any time, with reasonable notice to users of its website.  Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to our website.

**CUSTOMER CARE CONTACT INFORMATION:**

Please click here for information on how to contact us.

Policy Effective as of 11/01/14
